JUNBO KWON

kyle000603@gm.gist.ac.kr

Github: https://github.com/kyle000603

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I have strong interest on Computer Vision based on Natural Language Process methods. Especially, I am planning to make a novel method on CV with LLM.

I have strongly inspired to have various experience. I believe wide spectrum will affect creativity.

WORK HISTORY -

Research Intern, 01/2023 – 02/2023

ACSL @ GIST – Gwangju

Research on "Multi-Agent 3D Semantic Scene Graph Generator."

- Archive prior research for "3D Semantic Scene Graph Generator" and "Collaborative SLAM."
- Suggest idea of "Multi-Agent 3D Semantic Scene Graph Generator" based on "Efficient Decentralized SLAM."
- Participated in lab meetings and had presentation in lab seminars every months.

Intern, 09/2022 – 12/2022

ACSL at GIST - Gwangju

- Worked as study intern.
- Studied basic concept of Deeplearning and implemented models (CNN, RNN, etc) based on CS231n from Stanford University.
- With studied contents, had presentation every weeks.

Teaching Assistant, 03/2022 – 07/2022

GIST - Gwangju

- Work as TA for "Data Structure" course in GIST.
- Build codes for assignments and made test sets for lectures.

SKILLS

Programming Language:

- Python
- C++

Frameworks:

- PyTorch
- TensorFlow
- Matplotlib
- Numpy

Tools:

- Git
- Docker

Platform:

- Linux
- Mac

EDUCATION —	
Bachelor of Science: Electrical Engineering and Computer Science, 03/2020 - Current Gwangju Institute of Science And Technology - Gwangju, Republic Of Korea	
Summer International Visitor UG: Computer Science, 06/2022 – 08/2022 UC Berkeley - Berkeley, CA	
L	ANGUAGES —
English	Korean
Fluent	Native